Hi Evkini, can you hear me?
Hey, I know. Hello.
How are you doing?
Quite busy, but doing fine.
Yeah, yeah, I know. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you for, for making the time to meet with me real quick.
As you saw in the title, I'm running a summit rapid.
I will share like some documentation after I have the calls with all the exact team.
But basically working, gathering information to plan to lock or pencil the dates for the next summit.
And something I've been working with Paul is that we want to schedule like a region summit or a small
summit.
This is something we talked before about the engineering team to have a summit with them and the global summit.
So basically we're looking at two potential dates.
The first time frame would be late Q2 after we ship fundraising and for Global Summit Q4, around October, November.
So what I did real quick is something similar that what I did for last summit.
I prepared a spreadsheet with the potential dates and I have all the. Except in here.
So I want to know and understand better like if you have any, like if you have any personal plans
or travel already scheduled that we need to take into account.
So I could not really like I should be fine after like second part of April to travel.
Okay. Yeah. The dates we are looking at, it's May and June and then October, November.
Yeah, sounds good.
Yeah. So besides that I'm gonna add you as free on these dates. Even you have.
You don't have any plans yet and. Yeah, I mean that would be good. Yeah.
The thing is like for engineering summit, ideal location is most likely Poland because of like just flight costs and
other stuff.
So like if we will have dates, we need to start to work on visa process for a few people
as soon as possible.
Vlad, Ernie, like this is like two who come to mind that will need visas and it can take up
to 2, 3 months. Like so better like as soon as possible. They should be working on this.
Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense.
And that's why I'm gathering this info so we can start working on that as well.
Yeah, I think that Poland is best location for engineering summit, given location of most of you guys.
Is there any. Do you have any thoughts?
I was thinking that maybe we could also bring like a product design team for this summit as well.
But yeah, I don't know if you, you think that we should include anyone else to this.
Yeah, can be discussed. I think Megan makes sense to include Dennis. Like maybe product design team too.
Like it will slightly shift like the like goals of the summit. Right. Because it was just engineering.
Like it's like one way we like do like stuff.
And if they will be also designers, we'll also have to accommodate them too and like, you know, collaborate with
them too. So it will be slightly different way. But I'm fine. I'm fine either way.
Okay. And what about support? You don't think we should also include support team or at least N on this?
We can at least include N potentially. But again, like, if you're talking about like five days. Right. Okay.
Maybe Ann has like stuff to chat for one day with engineering team directly. Right? There's like no like.
Yeah, they interact a lot, but there is like not insane like amount of like touch points. Right.
There's like one interface how we communicate.
So if it's just like hang around, talk with engineers, tell them how she hates them because they don't like
her soft tickets in time, maybe it's a good idea.
But I mean, I think it's always good to have like in person collaboration and mostly because that like she's
part of your pod as well. So I mean, I think, I think it's.
I think it brings value at the end of the day because we keep growing like the in person relationship.
So yeah, I will have the conversation with her as well, like at a schedule time with her as well
to get her thoughts. So. Yeah. Okay. I think that's super valuable.
Evgeny, I mark you as free for the Both proposals for Q2 and Q4.
Keep me posted if you have any updates.
But yeah, I will try to work on getting decision as soon as possible so we can work on visas
if needed.
Okay, got it.
Okay, thank you so much. I'll keep you posted.
I will ship an update like a document with the proposals by next week. So yeah.
Monkey.
Bye. Bye.